OUR DEEPEST GRATITUDE
TO THE ROYAL MALAYSIAN POLICE (RMP)
FOR YOUR COOPERATION AND GUIDANCE
ALL NAMES, CHARACTERS,
INCIDENTS, AND STORIES
PORTRAYED IN THIS PRODUCTION
ARE A WORK OF FICTION
ANY RESEMBLANCE TO ACTUAL PERSONS,
LIVING OR DEAD OR ACTUAL EVENTS
IS PURELY COINCIDENTAL
Insufficient evidence.
FEDERAL COURT
Naz?
Hey.
What are you doing here?
So it's true.
You've been working for him all this time.
I came to see my informant.
You'd better leave now.
Informant?
Do you think I'm an idiot?
Look at that.
That gut.
It's bloated.
With the kickback you've been taking.
You wear the uniform every day.
With the insignia on your chest.
There's God.
There's the Prophet.
Have you no shame?
I would never, Naz.
You're out of your mind, Naz!
People like you aren't fit
to be police officers.
I'll write you up tonight
and tomorrow, you'll be suspended!
Naz!
Hear me out!
Because of people like you,
this world is damned!
ROYAL MALAYSIAN POLICE
POLICE
Come in.
Inspector Amirul Asyraff.
Yes?
How can I assist you?
I'm here to ask a few questions.
May I?
Of course, sir.
That's a beautiful car.
It's not that bad, sir.
It's secondhand.
Of course.
But this car is not cheap.
Especially with all those things.
It's expensive, right?
Courtesy of Sam Wukong?
Sam Wukong?
Who's that, sir?
Sam Wukong.
That gambling boss
you've been trying to nab?
Sir.
I have shut down quite a few
gambling dens, this year alone.
People don't go to dens these days.
Everything's online.
Right?
So now, are you accusing me?
Do you have evidence?
Evidence.
Here.
From Sam Wukong.
Evidence.
Transaction.
Every month.
To a company.
Which company?
This company.
And your name is right here.
I'm not done yet.
There's more.
Here's the audio recording
of Sam Wukong's confession.
Saying who has been covering for him
all this time.
It's you.
Do you know who gave me these?
The head of your department.
So what now?
Look at that.
That's your missus, right?
The photo looks nice.
After this…
I'm sure she'll ask for a divorce!
You'll definitely be divorced.
You're done!
Well…
This is what you get for taking bribes.
You're going to jail.
Have a seat, we're not done yet.
Where do you think you're going?
Put down your weapon!
Shut up!
You.
Easy for you to say!
You're of a higher rank!
Do you think my pay is enough?
The pay is not enough?
Stop!
Amirul Asyraff.
You are under arrest for accepting bribes
from an illegal business.
Anything you say
can and will be used
against you in the court of law.
-Sir.
-Yes.
Please, sir.
I've repented.
Praise be to God! Good for you.
POLICE
A murder victim has been discovered
in Kuala Lumpur.
And as you can see,
the police and the public
have arrived at the scene.
We have no information about the victim.
Chances are we'll be able to…
What time was the body found?
Around seven o'clock in the morning.
No witnesses.
The victim's car was found
300 m from here.
CCTV?
NARCOTICS
As usual.
He'll avoid places with CCTV.
What about DNA and fingerprints? Anything?
Nothing at all?
The body is thoroughly cleaned.
Just like before.
Why Sir Malik?
Could it be Sir Malik is corrupt?
-Watch your mouth.
-Sir.
Sir.
I'm sorry, sir.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I was just thinking about Sir Malik.
I feel sorry for his wife and kids.
As long as Tony is alive,
this country will never be peaceful.
Who is this?
If I'm not wrong,
people call him Kapak.
According to my informant,
he is Tony's new right-hand man.
Are you sure?
I've never seen him before.
Was he involved in many cases?
Quite a lot.
However,
we've never had enough evidence.
Can I get everyone's attention?
This is ASP Jennifer Wong,
from D1 Special Detective.
She will be working
the Meth Killer case with us.
Okay.
So there are eight victims
including Sir Malik,
suspected to have been killed
by the same murderer.
Code name,
Meth Killer.
The same technique is used,
stabbing the victims
several times in the abdomen,
then sprinkling meth
all over the dead body.
That's his signature.
Forensics also verified
that the meth on the victims' bodies
are from
Tony Ifrit.
The leader of the largest meth syndicate
in Malaysia.
We also know that
seven of the victims except Sir Malik,
according to your reports,
worked for Tony Ifrit,
who killed an undercover police officer,
Sub Inspector Syazwani.
Now,
I understand that the Narcotics Unit was
tasked to destroy Tony Ifrit's syndicate.
But I was assigned here
to find the Meth Killer.
Once again, Malaysia has been shaken
by the news of a serial killing
by a suspect known as the Meth Killer.
The eighth victim, a police officer,
Muhammad Malik bin Abdullah,
who was Head of the Narcotics Unit
for the RMP.
The police are still investigating--
I am
asking you
one more time.
Why didn't you meet up
with Malik that night?
I told you.
Someone called me
and said,
"Don't meet him."
He said…
it was your order.
Who called you?
I don't know.
He said he doesn't know, Kapak.
-Kapak.
-Yes, Boss.
I want you and the rest
to follow these dogs.
24-7.
Okay.
I don't know.
This is your opportunity to tell me.
God is the Greatest.
Blessed salutations, prayers,
good deeds to God.
I bear witness
that there is no deity but God.
ONLINE GAMBLING OPERATION
CASE CLOSED
-Sheriff, hurry up!
-Where are we going, Dad?
Hurry up!
Husin Osman!
Hands up!
Dad!
CORRUPTION CASES
Sheriff.
Sir.
A new case.
This case is complex.
NARCOTICS INTEGRITY OPERATION
But I am confident you are ready.
Okay, listen up.
I want you to start
following a few people tonight.
24-7.
Their pictures and addresses are here.
The ones you will be following
are police.
Remember, don't get caught.
Get lost.
Kapak.
What is it?
What else do you want?
How much longer
am I supposed to be an errand boy?
When are you going
to bring me to see Tony?
Hey.
The money I gave you isn't enough?
I just want to be like you.
To work at Tony's.
Bring me to see him, Kapak?
If you mention this again,
I'll blow your brains out!
Get lost!
Do you really think
what you're doing is right, Naz?
What you've done
won't change a thing!
Naz?
Naz!
Are you okay in there?
I'm okay.
Why are you taking so long?
I'm almost done!
Hurry up.
I need a ride.
My car is at the workshop.
Okay.
Hurry up.
Sya.
I read on the Internet…
-Many people--
-Support Meth Killer?
Saying what he did was right?
Haven't you noticed, Sya?
Since the Meth Killer appeared,
the crime rate for narcotics
dropped drastically?
That's murder, Naz.
It's wrong.
This country has laws.
Let the court decide,
not take matters into your own hands.
So what about Tony and his gang?
In and out of court,
getting away with it,
what law are you talking about?
You're the police.
If you don't trust the law,
what would become of our country?
Hey, boss. What do you want to eat?
-One fried rice.
-Okay, got it.
Drive.
If not, I'll blow your brains out.
I've told you, I don't know.
Don't tell me you know nothing.
Don't lie to me.
Don't lie to me!
Let's make things easy.
Are you going to tell me
where Tony's place is…
or not?
Nicky.
You forgot something?
Kamal Fakrul.
They call him Kapak.
One of Tony's guys who got promoted.
Do you know him?
Why is he not in the database?
We just identified him three days ago.
If we want to solve the case,
I need to know everything,
every goddamn details.
His data should've been updated yesterday.
I know.
But before any suspect is included
in Tony's crime syndicate,
we have to really make sure
that they're involved.
We can't just profile any drug dealer
and connect them to Tony as we please.
How did Naga get intel about Kapak?
He's got a lot of informants.
Come in.
You have a letter, ma'am.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
TONY IFRIT'S LOCATION
TONY'S ROOM
This is from the Meth Killer for sure.
Should we trust them?
But what if
it's legit?
They killed Sir Malik!
We are not breaking any laws
if we act on this intel
to raid the place.
What about ASP Jane, sir?
Her task is to catch the Meth Killer.
Our task
is to destroy Tony's syndicate.
This info is confidential
for the time being.
For now,
don't tell anyone.
So what should we do, sir?
We'll raid this place tonight.
-Sya.
-Sir.
Okay.
According to this floor plan,
this is the entrance.
We will enter through the back.
Police! Don't move!
Engage only with armed suspects.
Down!
Don't move!
Stop what you're doing!
Farouk, Sir Hafsham and myself,
we'll take care of the front.
When you have secured the middle area,
one of you will enter Tony's room.
But please be careful.
There will be guards.
And most importantly,
we must capture Tony Ifrit
alive.
Naz.
Naz?
Are you okay with the plan?
What are we waiting for?
Where are you guys going?
We have training.
I want you guys
to get back to your office.
This training is important.
This is an order from the higher-ups.
The highest.
I'm from RMP's Special Unit.
You guys know, right?
I am the police who arrests…
police.
My name is Sheriffudin Husin.
You can just call me Sheriff.
Sounds fictitious!
Farouk Mahmud right?
You've got a problem with my name?
Starting today,
I'll be working with ASP Jane
to solve this case.
I'm telling you that the Meth Killer
is actually from the Narcotics Department.
Hold on a second.
Why is it us, not outsiders?
How could it be an outsider?
How would they know
the hierarchy of Tony's organization?
Including this.
Sir Malik.
Who is likely
corrupted.
Hey, do you even have proof
he's corrupted?
Nagarajan!
Sit down.
Have a seat. I'm just getting started.
Have you heard of the name, Wan Daniel?
In 1998, Wan Daniel committed
nine murders involving drug dealers
and pushers.
He kills the same way.
He kills and scatters drugs
all over the body.
So the Meth Killer
is Wan Daniel?
No.
He was caught
and hanged.
But before that, he gave a statement.
He wanted to deliver a message
to the police.
It was,
"Whoever is involved in drugs
and corruption deserves to be killed."
So after I read your reports and records,
you lot
have the highest potential
for being made a suspect.
Why us?
What's the connection
between the Meth Killer and us?
Since Farouk Mahmud
has so much to say today,
I'll start the interrogation
with you, okay?
On the night of June 28th,
where were you? What were you doing?
You're wasting your time, sir.
We have a lot of work to do.
Oh no.
I forgot.
I was at home.
Why?
What's the problem?
Any witnesses?
Yes. My wife.
Yes.
My brother.
Witness?
I cannot remember.
I came back from the office
with my sister.
And then I went out,
ordered some takeout,
went home,
ate, and went to bed.
Look at these!
Medical certificates,
annual leave, emergency leave.
It's only the middle of the month,
what's the deal?
I have stomach aches.
Probably gastric.
You still can't remember?
What kind of police are you?
I already told you.
-I cannot remember.
-Based on the records, you have issues.
Anger issues.
You've argued with Sir Malik.
What's that about?
I argued
because there are things I disagree.
Just a little bit more…
Am I not allowed to question anything?
Are you kidding me?
Were you already thinking
of a promotion, sir?
Given that Sir Malik
is out of the picture.
Watch your mouth.
Sir Malik
is like my own brother.
May 4th, 2023.
I already told you, I can't remember!
I'm a human being.
I'm not a robot.
I went to the movies with my friend.
I didn't keep the tickets.
But you can check the mall's CCTV.
Last month, you've settled
all of your debts with the bank.
Damned if I do, damned if I don't.
What do you actually want?
ASP Syazlin.
Can you explain
what happened in this video?
You said you went to the movies.
What movie was it?
Hujan di Kuala Lumpur
directed by Faizal Nuar.
Who is the hero?
Hassan Mutalib.
How long was the movie?
Two hours.
Who is your friend?
Iman.
Where did you meet?
At school.
Why did you meet your friend?
Can't I meet my friends, sir?
Okay.
So far,
there's only one potential suspect.
ASP Syazlin.
Sya.
Are you still keeping quiet?
May 4th, 2023, at 11 p.m.
ASP Syazlin entered Sir Malik's office.
It seemed like Sir Malik asked ASP Syazlin
to take off her jacket.
He realized there was a CCTV
and switched it off.
About 15 minutes later,
we can see ASP Syazlin walking slowly,
exiting Sir Malik's office.
So…
you still don't want to talk about it?
What did he do to you?
I've told you.
Nothing happened.
We were just discussing an operation.
Okay.
All of you, relax.
You are all still
potential suspects.
We have a lot of different behaviors.
Some have
anger issues,
some are senile.
And ASP Syazlin
has a strong alibi
for those dates
when the Meth Killer
killed their victims.
So I'm using a scoring system
for all potential suspects.
Some have high scores,
some have low scores.
But there is only one among all
who got a perfect score.
Just one.
That person is…
Let's give a round of applause
to Inspector…
Nazri.
Just like
how the Meth Killer works.
So what are you trying to say?
Nothing.
Dismissed.
Sya.
What happened in that room?
I don't want to talk about it.
What's the situation, Naga?
It's empty.
They're gone.
They've just cleared out.
The machine is still warm.
How did they know?
If Sheriff didn't interfere,
we would've nabbed them!
What are you doing here?
I tailed you.
You didn't notice?
You shouldn't interfere in our operations.
This is important.
At first, it was training.
Now, it's an operation.
So which one is it?
Enough.
To hell with your problems!
The info you gave me
is just too slow!
You are no use to me!
My machine is worth millions, damn it.
Millions!
Stupid dog.
You piece of shit.
That damn Meth Killer
keeps messing with my business.
If you don't want me to come after you,
you'd better find him!
Now!
You.
Why didn't you bring along the machine?
I didn't have time, boss, I swear!
Go look for the machine tonight!
And you.
Make sure of it.
Why are you looking at him?
I'm disgusted.
Why?
I hate his beard.
Look!
Wannabe gangster beard.
Maybe he did a lot of undercover work.
Under…
You don't need to defend him.
Do you guys know?
I did a background check.
His dad got shot
because he ran away with bribe money.
So you're saying he was the one
who leaked our info yesterday?
If the dad took bribes,
don't you think the son wouldn't?
Guys.
Actually,
I have something to tell you.
Since this morning,
Sheriff has been going to the washroom.
Seven or eight times.
Something's wrong somewhere.
Slackers.
Is he going to the washroom again?
How dare you?
Taking drugs in the police station!
And you call yourself
an integrity police officer?
The gall…
Taking drugs in the station.
And you accused us of being murderers.
Hey.
Why are you not answering?
Do you think you're better than us?
You messed up our operation yesterday.
You're cocky.
And arrogant.
Just you wait. I'll throw you in jail!
Junkie.
Release him.
Sir.
It's ibuprofen.
For migraines.
Give me a minute.
I want to look at all these faces.
Hold up.
What about these?
Uncuff him.
Sir.
Uncuff him now.
But sir.
He took it like this, sir.
Was I?
I was told,
if I did it like that,
I'd recover faster.
This case is so complicated,
it's doing my head in.
That's why I need to take it.
Damn, what are you playing at?
Naz!
Everyone, stay calm. We don't want a riot.
Calm down.
For now…
I'd like everyone
to step out of the room.
Because Nazri and I
have
something to discuss.
Everyone.
Thank you.
Happy now?
You played us.
What exactly do you want?
I just wanted to see
who would arrest me.
But you were so enthusiastic.
So earnest.
What did you expect?
I'm a narcotics police officer.
And you're the integrity police!
Taking meds like that looks bad.
You should know better.
Do you know what's worse?
Police that violate ethics.
That's bad.
Police that take bribes.
But the worst is…
police that kill.
Are you accusing me?
Without evidence,
your accusations don't stand in court.
This is Malaysia, Naz.
Even the Prime Minister goes to prison.
Why do you suspect Nazri?
Sya still doesn't have an answer
about the CCTV.
Naz.
Anything you want to tell me?
About what?
The department knows Sheriff suspects you.
Suspect me of what?
That I'm the Meth Killer?
I noticed you're always out at night.
Where did you go?
You're accusing me of being a murderer
because I always go out at night?
Instead of accusing me,
tell me what Sir Malik
did to you in his room.
I'm not accusing you.
But if the evidence is there,
whether it's a friend,
a family member,
or even my own brother,
I will arrest them.
C-L-E-A-R?
C-L-E-A-R.
Are you sure Sheriff is not following you?
I'm sure.
I'm not followed.
You still haven't updated me
on Tony's location.
I've told you many times,
I'm just an errand boy.
When I gave you Kapak,
you guys were slow!
Are you high?
I told you to stop.
What do you expect?
Nine people are dead, damn it!
I can't help it, Naz.
Hey, what's the matter with you?
Are you afraid?
Hey, are you afraid?
Where's your fighting spirit?
You're the one who said to me
what we're doing is right.
Hey, Naz.
If you get caught,
you'll only be arrested.
If I get caught, Tony will chop me up!
I'll be dead meat, you know?
You know how Tony is.
Hey.
With Sheriff suddenly turning up
and Tony changing locations,
do you realize that there's a rat
in your department?
A rat!
I can't do it anymore, Naz.
I just can't.
I can't help you anymore.
Okay, Daus, here's the deal.
-Daus, listen to me.
-Damn you.
Listen to me. Here's the deal.
This is our last deal and after this,
you won't have to help me anymore.
After you've read it, burn it.
Hey.
Here he is.
Please come in.
Please.
Take a seat.
Right here.
Okay.
Jane, would you?
Nor Syazwani.
Sub Inspector of Narcotics Department.
Killed last year in an undercover mission.
Someone from this department
blew Inspector Wani's cover.
Your girlfriend?
That's why you killed Sir Malik.
Is this all for revenge?
What are you on about?
Who said she's my girlfriend?
She's not your girlfriend?
Really? Not your girlfriend?
Are you sure?
Okay.
Jane.
Play the video.
Dear Narcotics Department.
This is the repercussion
when you send an undercover
to our headquarters.
She's not crying?
That's cool.
Let's all take turns with her
and make her pregnant!
Let's see if she is going to cry.
What are you waiting for?
Get her on the table!
Hold her legs!
Hold tight.
Rip her clothes off! Take them off!
Rip them off!
Let me go!
God is the Greatest!
There is no God here.
God!
God is the Greatest!
Stop that video! This is too much!
This is part of our investigation
and you are not involved!
Stop that video!
Jane, stop the video.
You're good.
You watched that video
and you managed to keep a straight face.
Sheriff.
You know that's a police officer, right?
From the first day,
she knew the consequences and risks.
Yesterday,
you were just a suspect.
Today,
I found a motive.
Tomorrow?
I'll definitely find proof.
Why don't you just confess?
Cut the story short.
-Sir.
-Yes?
The Meth Killer.
Sir, we have set up
a 2 km radius roadblock.
A witness saw a body
being removed from a green sedan.
The wounds look fresh.
He has been dead for about an hour or two.
What do you think?
Are we all still suspects?
We were at the office since morning.
-Sir.
-Yes?
There are traces of flesh
under the victim's fingernails, sir.
Send that to the lab for a DNA test.
Sir!
We have tracked down the suspect.
He was stopped at a roadblock
on Maluri Street.
Hong, give me your keys.
Let's go!
There goes your bike.
The suspect is holding a hostage.
He is armed.
I repeat, he is armed.
Copy, over.
Put your gun down!
Drop your weapon!
Do you guys want her dead?
Calm down, mister!
I'll shoot her!
Damn you!
Step on it!
Damn you, police!
Come out!
There goes your car.
Hey!
Leave me alone, you dogs!
Where do you think you're going?
Get in.
Naz, are you okay?
I'm okay.
We finally found the Meth Killer.
Naz.
Could you handle the interrogation?
Could you? Is there a problem?
Sure, no problem.
Here are the questions.
Naz.
Just go in, okay?
"Firdaus bin Ishak.
Single.
Army veteran.
Arrested two years ago.
Suspected involvement
with Tony Ifrit's meth syndicate."
Correct?
S-I-L-E-N-C-E.
"Why were you resisting arrest?"
"Are you the serial killer
known as the Meth Killer?"
S-I-L-E-N-C-E.
"If the DNA is a match
and you are found guilty,
you…
will be sentenced
to death
by hanging."
S-I-L-E-N-C-E.
I…
Why are you not answering?
Answer me!
Say something!
Naz!
Break it up!
-Damn it! Answer me!
-Calm down!
Say something!
Get the medics.
Get the medics!
Hey, you!
Why did you shoot him?
He was going to attack you!
Inspector Farouk has been suspended.
Harder, kid. I can't feel it.
That's it.
What a bummer.
Turn the music off.
I said turn the music off!
Since we stopped production, I thought
the whole of KL would be out of stock.
But apparently,
all the other drug dealers are scared.
And the price of my stuff went up!
I thought the Meth Killer
would ruin my business, but no.
I didn't expect to make a bank.
Boss, we don't have enough pushers.
Zack is dead.
Kids.
Line up.
Good, this is what I like, discipline.
Teach these imbeciles how to make money.
I'll give you kids,
a special kind of candy.
After you've tasted the candy,
you're going to sell it.
Right now I want you
to turn these kids into addicts.
And let them be our pushers.
I would like to see
if the Meth Killer kills kids.
Get on it, you fools!
I've got an announcement.
I want all of you to follow me downstairs.
Both officers and personnel.
You two, get in.
You'll be sleeping here tonight, okay?
Yes, sir.
Jane.
Two of my guys
who has been tailing you home
will stay here
tonight.
I won't be following you.
And they won't be following you too.
What are you trying to do?
I just got back from the forensics morgue.
The DNA found under the victim's nails
belongs to Firdaus bin Ishak.
So…
Firdaus is indeed the Meth Killer.
No.
The method is different.
The stabs are not precise, it seems like…
it was forced.
Actually, the Meth Killer is still here
among us.
What are you playing at?
No, this is not a game.
I think you might have guessed it
why your operations constantly fail.
In this department,
we have a traitor
who works for Tony.
A rat.
So listen carefully.
To the traitor who works for Tony,
tell your boss
that I really want to work together.
I want to see him.
Tell him, I can get him
the Meth Killer.
That's all.
You said the Meth Killer is dead.
So what now?
What?
Who is this DSP Sheriff?
Why does he want to see me?
He wants to cooperate.
To find the Meth Killer.
All right then.
Tell me about Sheriff.
He's really good, Tony.
But you have
to be careful with him.
I gave you one job.
Is that so difficult?
If you tell me who your other rat is,
my job will be much easier.
But you won't tell me.
So I need more time.
She is the Meth Killer.
Okay, I know it.
I just don't have the evidence.
Why her?
Why not her brother,
that damn narcotics dog?
Because she's hiding something.
I can see it from her face.
Jane.
Oh, Jane.
Never forget where you came from.
If my rat finds out about your betrayal,
your bastard son
will be dead.
Now, take her away.
What a waste of time.
Get in.
I'm doing the right thing.
I'm…
I'm doing the right thing!
I'm not guilty.
It's not a sin.
I'm doing the right thing!
Have a seat, Naz.
Forgive me, Sya.
For asking you to take off your jacket.
We don't know who is listening in on us.
What's the matter, sir?
I know the whole department
is suspecting me.
Yes, I am Tony Ifrit's rat.
Here's the proof.
But I did it to obtain Tony's location.
What about Wani?
Wani died.
It wasn't me
who leaked the info about Wani, Sya.
My undercover operation
is known by the superiors.
What do you mean, sir?
There's another rat who works for Tony.
A traitor in our department.
The Meth Killer
has killed six victims, Sya.
I doubt I can keep
my identity hidden any longer.
If they're wrong,
they might kill me.
And if I am killed,
it proves that the Meth Killer
is in our department.
Why are you telling me this, sir?
I trust you.
I doubt you'll kill your brother's lover.
If anything happens to me,
hand over this money
and this recorder
to the Special Branch, understand?
Understood, sir.
But remember, Sya.
Don't trust anyone.
Even if it's your own brother.
All this while, I have never suspected
your sister.
Based on the intelligence
that your sister shared with the SB,
the IGP told me to handle this case.
Naz.
You have to remember
that what the Meth Killer is doing
is wrong.
He killed
an undercover police officer, Naz.
Naz.
What's the difference
between the Meth Killer
and Wani's murderer?
If you're still a police officer,
come tomorrow
and confess.
Confess?
Did I do something wrong?
That's enough, Naz.
Where's your evidence?
Your motive
is too strong.
If there's no evidence,
your accusations don't stand in--
Court?
Yes, I know that.
I'll lose.
You're really good, Naz.
But
I know deep down,
you
are not a bad person.
There's still
integrity in you.
Am I right?
You have until tomorrow, Naz.
If you don't confess,
I'll do it the hard way.
I've got no other choice.
You killed me.
You killed innocent people.
Confess, Naz.
DSP
Sheriff.
Tony Ifrit.
Let him go.
Let go of him!
I want to get acquainted with DSP Sheriff.
Hey.
Look at me.
Good fight.
But as we all know,
life is never fair.
Let's talk business.
Hold on a minute.
Before that.
Was it necessary to hit my car?
Let me see.
I forgot.
I don't take bribes.
So how?
Hey, just keep it.
Hey.
You said
you can get me the Meth Killer.
That's right.
Okay, so what do you need?
I need
the name of your rat.
That's all.
No.
Here's the thing.
There are too many suspects.
At least if I get a name,
I have one less suspect.
Get the board.
Show him.
Like the police.
This punk is the Meth Killer, right?
Him?
No.
It's a 100% no.
He has a strong alibi.
Okay.
What about her?
Hang on.
Maybe yes.
Maybe no.
I can't be sure.
Are you messing with me?
I don't kill police.
Unless I'm forced to.
This is your reminder.
Now, give me a name.
Jennifer Wong.
Not possible.
Why?
Is she your rat?
Here's the thing, Tony.
You want the Meth Killer, right?
I'm sure your rat has told you
that I'm this close
to nabbing the Meth Killer.
So…
just give me some info.
Make my job easy.
My rats
don't know each other.
There are two.
You've got two of them.
Gosh.
Got it.
You're dangerous.
You're a dangerous man.
A very dangerous man.
Please don't say that.
Take him away now!
Before he dies here.
I need to leave? I just--
Sheriff.
You have until 2 p.m.
If you can't find the Meth Killer,
you'll know what I'll do.
A little bit more info.
Never trust police officers
who don't take bribes.
That's enough, Naz.
Until tomorrow, Naz.
Just confess, Naz.
Do the right thing, Naz.
Looking for this?
How long have you been off your meds?
Don't worry.
I won't tell Sheriff.
Look.
I believe in the Meth Killer.
I believe
you're doing the right thing.
And people like Tony
don't deserve to live.
Now, I can give you what you want.
But in return, you have to trust me.
Naga, did you finish checking the CCTV?
It's confirmed, sir.
Naz's car entered the car park
at 7:30 a.m.
He left 15 minutes later at 7:45 a.m.
Hong.
Sir, I called Jane a few times.
She's not picking up.
Call her one more time. Anything?
Nothing. No info from roadblocks.
Where is he?
Sya.
Naz didn't tell you where he was going?
When I woke up this morning,
he wasn't home.
What if we got played?
What's wrong, Sya?
I received a link.
Narcotics Department.
You recognize this kid, don't you?
Don't you?
Good.
I'll provide 2 locations
by 10 p.m. tonight.
The first location
is for my boys to pick up the Meth Killer.
The second location
is for that damn Sheriff
and his narcotics dogs.
But remember.
If by the time my boys arrive
and the Meth Killer does not surrender,
this kid will die.
That's a promise.
One more thing.
If Sheriff doesn't show up
at the given location,
Jane will die.
Sheriff.
Don't try to outsmart me.
I'm really annoyed.
Jane.
Are you sure he's not the Meth Killer?
A hundred percent.
Either way, you're still going to die.
Ask our boys to be on standby.
We are going to have
narcotics dogs for dinner.
Sir.
Didn't you suspect
Naz was the Meth Killer?
If Naz is Meth Killer,
who does Tony want exactly?
Naz
is not Meth Killer.
Sya.
I met Tony last night.
He said
there's more than one rat in your unit.
There are two.
If he knows Naz is the Meth Killer,
Naz will be killed.
So what's your plan?
-This is not the time to think, Sheriff.
-Just give me a minute.
This is dangerous.
I've always suspected Jane was the rat.
Do you have proof?
What if she's not the rat?
Are you willing to risk it?
We're out of time.
But I have a plan.
Let me be the Meth Killer.
This operation is very risky, Sya.
One location for Sheriff's team.
And another for the Meth Killer.
The distance between these 2 locations
are approximately 20 km.
Organized Crime Group
will use the usual tactics.
We don't know where
they're taking ASP Syazlin.
But don't worry.
We placed a tracker.
07 to 06.
OCG has picked up ASP Sya.
OCG has picked up ASP Sya. Over.
Meth Killer.
A woman.
I have longed to meet you.
Do you want to know why?
Where is my brother?
Your brother is dead.
What's the matter?
Are you upset?
When you killed my boys,
you thought I was not angry?
Their lives belong to me, damn it!
Hong.
The coordinates
are precisely those of the bus.
Naga.
Do you see anything?
There's movement, sir.
Sniper.
Sniper to Eagle.
No movement.
Negative.
Jane.
You're up.
You have to remember.
In this world,
evil always wins.
Do you want to know why?
Because when good people like you
resort to evil ways,
those like me
will become
the Devil!
God is the Greatest.
Sniper, scope!
Sniper, fall back!
Hong!
Damn you!
You've known him for a long time!
I've told you.
He will kill my son!
Right now,
you have Tony right in front of you.
You can do whatever you want to me,
but only after you kill him!
That's our deal, right?
Do you want to kill me now?
Who said I wanted to kill you?
I don't want to kill you.
I want to torture you.
Slowly.
I want you to become my slave.
My toy.
A toy for my boys
until they are satisfied.
You swallowed the tracker?
Move!
Fall back!
Move it!
Move!
Hong!
-Hong!
-Go!
Grenade!
Go to hell!
Hold!
Now!
Target moving. 100.
Sniper, on your time.
Sniper on scope!
Move forward!
Go!
Sniper to Eagle.
Perimeter secured.
Cover me!
Bastard!
Come out!
Come out, you coward!
Don't be afraid.
I'm the police.
Kid.
Hey, kid.
Don't go anywhere.
Stay here.
Don't come out.
Go to hell!
Eagle to Delta.
Eagle to Delta, come in!
Step on it!
You've picked the wrong dragon.
If I die,
my boys will hunt you
and your sister
until you're dead.
If you let me go,
I'll give you the money.
You can't buy me, Tony.
I'm the Meth Killer, you fool!
I…
I guessed as much.
Use your laws,
take me to court.
How many times have you gone
in and out of court, Tony?
This time, I'll be the law.
Wait a minute.
If you want to kill me, do it.
But I'm content.
I've tasted your girlfriend.
She tastes good.
So damn good!
Naz!
Sya.
Sya!
Naz!
Sya.
Sya, help me, Sya!
You're truly no good, aren't you?
You wanted to kill Sya.
Put your hands up!
Throw away your gun.
Naz.
-Listen to me--
-Shut up!
Get down.
Naz!
Put down your gun.
Sya.
She tried to shoot you.
-Jane is Tony's rat.
-Sya.
Listen to me.
Okay?
He's mentally ill. I found his meds, Sya.
Shut up!
She's known Tony for a long time.
She confessed she's Tony's rat!
I'm an undercover, Sya.
You can ask the SB or Sheriff.
Shut up, you traitor!
You have to believe me, Sya.
How can I believe you?
You've lied to me all this time!
This country has laws, Naz.
Put that gun down.
What laws, Sya?
Is this the same law that has failed us?
Sya, people like her,
don't deserve to live.
This country needs people like me, Sya.
Jane!
Don't you dare move.
Sya.
-I…
-Don't move!
You said you're undercover, right?
It's okay.
We'll see.
Jane!
Sorry, I was late.
I didn't expect you to be the other rat.
There are a lot of bodies.
How are we going to cover it up?
Medic!
The shootout at Tony Ifrit's headquarters
resulted in the death
of ten RMP Special Force agents.
Meanwhile, the flash operation
by the RMP Special Unit
killed four police officers.
ASP Syazlin was shot by Farouk Mahmud,
a former police officer
who conspired with Tony Ifrit.
This was confirmed
by the burner phone found in his pocket.
His last call
was from the burner phone of Tony Ifrit,
who was killed by the Meth Killer.
Forensics confirmed that the bullets fired
from Nazri Mutalib's gun
pierced the agents of Special Force
and several of Tony Ifrit's subordinates.
This proves that
Nazri Mutalib is the Meth Killer.
Five out of six abducted children
are now safe.
In conclusion,
the largest meth syndicate led
by Tony Ifrit has been dismantled
and the case of the Meth Killer
is now solved.
That's all from me, ASP Jennifer Wong.
But 14 police officers died in this case.
They are the real heroes.
My department will make
the final assessment
based on the evidence that was reported.
If everything's in order,
only then can we close both cases.
Thank you.
All dismissed.
ASP.
Congratulations. You solved the case.
Thank you.
I couldn't have done it without you guys.
Gosh, no.
It's just that
I feel sorry for Sya.
She should not have died.
She was…
She was a good police officer.
Hey, she still doesn't know.
What is it?
But the doctor said in two or three days,
she'll be stable.
But why wasn't I told?
We thought you knew.
All right, ma'am.
We need to go.
Hey, Jane. When did you get here?
Hey, I just got here.
I came straight away
when I heard Sya survived.
Okay.
Jane.
Now may not be the right time and place.
But…
I do have a few questions for you.
May I?
When I went to Tony's old place,
I found this.
A ripped receipt
for Iris International School.
The same school you send your son to.
What do you think?
It's merely a coincidence.
Maybe yes.
Maybe no.
Maybe you've been working for Tony
for a while now.
Because
this receipt is dated from four years ago.
Does it have my name?
Or my son's?
You're here to actually kill Sya, right?
You were going to poison her
with
these fruits.
Right?
Sheriff, if you want,
take them to the lab.
And check if there's poison.
All right.
Next question.
You said you and Naz were kidnapped
by Tony.
Right?
Both are in the same car.
And you saw Tony gave orders
to his boys, correct?
Yes.
If so, then you must be
familiar with
the thing Tony uses regularly.
This box contains
Tony's meth pipe.
Did you notice him using it?
How could I?
Jane.
Surely you've noticed.
Tony and his pipe are like this…
If you say that you were kidnapped,
what's your proof if you don't even know
this thing?
What's it going to be, Jane?
Come on.
In your report,
you wrote that you saw him.
Here's the deal, Jane.
If you can guess
the color
of Tony's favorite pipe
in this box,
I won't ask questions anymore.
I will assume
that you were indeed kidnapped by Tony.
Okay?
Take a guess.
Okay.
Let's see.
You're right.
But I stole this pipe
when I met Tony.
Before you were kidnapped.
How could you have known
the color?
You've known Tony
for a long time, haven't you?
Your tales about what went down at Tony's…
That was impressive.
If only I had a witness…
This case
could have been settled by now.
Oh dear!
Jane.
Why don't we ask Sya?
Who knows, maybe she could be a witness?
Sya, could you?
We've got a witness.
We've got a motive.
We've got evidence.
Your poison for Sya is also right here.
It's over. You're done.
I suddenly feel parched.
I'll have a glass of water.
Why is it so difficult?
Just confess.
Stop.
Don't drink it.
There's poison.
Enough!
Don't go too far!
Jane.
Listen carefully.
Don't be foolish.
You won't get away with it.
Your gun.
Put it down.
I know too much of Tony's secrets.
Tony is dead.
Your son is safe.
Put down
the gun.
If they find out
you're still going to investigate me,
they would still kill my son!
They?
Don't trust anyone, Sheriff.
Take care of my son.
Jane!
Hi, Nick.
Hey.
Hi.
How was school?
You want to know something, Nick?
I used to study here.
-Really?
-Yes. Really.
I know for now,
it's boring,
no friends, and all that.
But once you have a lot of friends,
you won't even want to go home.
Hey, you are strong. You can do this.
Okay? Don't be sad.
All right?
MEMORIES, INTEGRITY
If I were you, Sya,
I don't know
if I'd be able to do what you did.
This case has taught me a lot.
The law is still the law.
And that no one is perfect.
That's why
you're the best person
to serve this department.
I'll do my best, sir.
-Sheriff, Sya.
-Sir.
We have secured cooperation with
the Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission.
But remember.
A suspect is innocent until proven guilty.
FEDERAL COURT
Peace be upon you, sir.
Peace be upon you too.
Are you Dr. Syed Abdul Rahman?
Yes, I am.
Sir, we're the police.
Can we ask a few questions?
What do you want to ask?